A Guide to the United States Circuit Court (5th Circuit) Court records, 1790-1882
Library of Virginia
- Series VIII. Record books, 1790-1869., Extent: 21 volumes on shelf. (Volume on shelf)
  - Record book No. 9I, 1799 November. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3952))
  - Record book No. 10, 1816 May. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3952))
  - Record book No. 11, 1816 November-1817 December. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3953))
  - Record book No. 12, 1817 November-1818 May. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3954))
  - Record book No. 13, 1818 May-December. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3955))
  - Record book No. 14, 1821 May-June. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3955))
  - Record book No. 15, 1821 November-1822 June. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3956))
  - Record book No. 16, 1824 November-1825 June. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3956))
  - Record book No. 17, 1825 November-1826 June. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3957))
  - Record book No. 18, 1826 November-1829 June. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3957))
  - Record book No. 19, 1829 November-1832 June. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3958))
  - Record book No. 20, 1832 May-1834 December. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 3958))
  - Record book No. A, 1866 May-1869 November. (Volume on shelf)
  - Record book No. A, Index, 1866 May-1869 November. (Volume on shelf)
- Series IX. Rules books, 1790-1854., Extent: 5 volumes on shelf. (Volume on shelf)
  The volume entries include listings for each case, name of attorney, marshalls return, bail taken, plaintiff and defendant names, types of cases, and a time line of the case month by month (ie continued, plea taken, etc.).
  - Rules book No. 1, 1790 November-1799 May. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 812))
  - Rules book No. 2, 1799 November-1802 April. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 812))
  - Rules book No. 3, 1823 May-1827 February. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 812))
  - Rules book No. 4, 1833 May-1844 May. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 812))
  - Rules book No. 5, 1844 May-1845; 1854 October. (Volume on shelf (Also on Misc. reel 812))